Guide to the Antone's: Home of the Blues Collection
The Wittliff Collections
Antone's: Home of the Blues Collection
2003-2004
The Wittliff Collections https://www.thewittliffcollections.txstate.edu
Silver Star Entertainment (Firm); Tomblin, Anthony "Lucky"
SWWC.095
3 Linear Feet
13 boxes
Material related to the production and marketing of Antone's: Home of the Blues, including 318 DV cam tapes of raw footage used in the production of the film, DVD viewing copies of the DV cam tapes, one commercial DVD copy of the documentary, one poster for the premiere, critical reviews, press releases, short bios and a list of the cast, video trailer, TV news report, and a VHS copy of the first cut that premiered at the South by Southwest film festival in March 2004.
Scope and Contents
The SilverStar Entertainment Group Antone's: Home of the Blues Collection contains materials used in the production and release of the documentary film, Antone's: Home of the Blues. The bulk of the collection is video recordings of performances, interviews and other raw footage used to produce the film. The collection is arranged into three series: Production Videos, Marketing and Publicity, and Documentary.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research.
Source of Acquisition
Gift of Anthony "Lucky" Tomblin, 2007
Other Descriptive Information
The DV cam tapes were transferred to DVDs for patron viewing purposes. Most DVDs fit two DV cam tapes each. Almost all the tapes have two versions with identical content recorded with different cameras—"Camera A" and "Camera B." In most cases only the Camera A tapes were transferred to DVD.
Biographical Note
Clifford Antone opened the music venue, Antone's, in Austin, Texas in 1975, at the age of 25. The venue was one of the first on Austin's 6th Street and contributed to the city's establishment as the "Live Music Capital of the World." Some of the artists that performed at Antone's include Fats Domino, John Lee Hooker, Delbert McClinton, Pinetop Perkins, Muddy Waters, Albert Collins, Jimmy Reed, Clarence "Gatemouth" Brown, B.B. King and many other famous blues musicians. Antone also helped launch the careers of Jimmie and Stevie Ray Vaughan.
In 1987, Antone started the Antone's record label and record store in Austin, still in operation on Guadaulpe Street. He also was active with numerous social and educational organizations, such hosting fundraisers for disadvantaged youths and teaching classes at local universities and colleges. Antone passed away on May 23, 2006, but the club remains open, at its third location, on W. 5th Street in Austin. In 2009, Antone was indicted into the Blues Hall of Fame in Memphis, Tennessee.
Anthony "Lucky" Tomblin, is a songwriter and the lead vocalist of The Lucky Tomblin Band. In the 1980s, he founded The Fire Station recording studio in San Marcos, Texas, and produced albums for artists such as the Texas Tornados, Joe Ely, Flaco Jimenez, and Jerry Jeff Walker. Lucky was the Executive Producer of the independent film, Antone's: Home of the Blues.
Antone's: Home of the Blues was directed by Dan Karlock and produced by Colleen Saro. It premiered at the 2004 South by Southwest film festival in Austin, Texas. Through archival footage, contemporary interviews and performances both old and new, the documentary chronicles Clifford Antone and the legendary blues club he founded in 1975.
Index Terms
Subjects
Documentary films -- Production and direction; Blues (Music) -- Texas; Musicians -- Interviews
Subjects (Persons)
Tomblin, Anthony "Lucky"; Antone, Clifford
- Interview and Performance Videos, 2003; 13299
  Series Description
  This series consists of 318 DV cam tapes of raw footage used in the production of the film, as well as DVD viewing copies and inventories of the tapes.
  - Blues Boy Hubbard interview (Box 1, Item 1a)
  - Blues Boy Hubbard interview – wide master (Box 1, Item 1b)
  - Blues Boy Hubbard interview continued (Box 1, Item 2a)
  - Blues Boy Hubbard interview continued (Box 1, Item 2b)
  - Blues Boy Hubbard playing solo – A camera only -beginning of Guy Forsyth interview part I (Box 1, Item 3a)
  - Guy Forsyth interview continued (Box 1, Item 4a)
  - Guy Forsyth interview (Box 1, Item 4b)
  - Clifford interview at law offices, March 21, 2003 (Box 1, Item 5a)
  - Clifford interview at law offices, master shot, March 21, 2003 (Box 1, Item 5b)
  - Tommy Shannon interview, March 21, 2003 (Box 1, Item 6a)
  - Tommy Shannon interview / B camera only - Tommy & Clifford hugging at beginning of tape and watching TV at end of tape, March 21, 2003 (Box 1, Item 6b)
  - Malford Milligan interview at Austin to Boston Studio, March 21, 2003 (Box 1, Item 7a)
  - Malford Milligan interview at Austin to Boston Studio, March 21, 2003 (Box 1, Item 7b)
  - Clifford interview #2 at law office, March 22, 2003 (Box 1, Item 8a)
  - Clifford interview #2 at law office, March 22, 2003 (Box 1, Item 8b)
  - Clifford interview #2, March 22, 2003 (Box 1, Item 9a)
  - Clifford interview #2, March 22, 2003 (Box 1, Item 9b)
  - Bob Schneider at Antone's, A camera only, March 22, 2003 (Box 1, Item 10)
  - BB King (Box 1, Item 11a)
  - BB King (Box 1, Item 11b)
  - WC Clark interview part I (Box 1, Item 12a)
  - WC Clark (Box 1, Item 12b)
  - WC Clark interview part 2 (Box 1, Item 13a)
  - WC Clark (Box 1, Item 13b)
  - Blue Monday, March 24, 2003 (Box 1, Item 14a)
  - Blue Monday part I, March 24, 2003 (Box 1, Item 14b)
  - Charlie interview/TC Breck, end of Blue Monday (Box 1, Item 15a)
  - Charlie interview/TC Breck Blue Monday (Box 1, Item 15b)
  - Margaret Moser interview, March 25, 2003 (Box 1, Item 16a)
  - Margaret Moser interview, March 25, 2003 (Box 2, Item 16b)
  - Bob Schneider, March 25, 2003 (Box 2, Item 17a)
  - Bob Schneider interview, March 25, 2003 (Box 2, Item 17b)
  - Exterior Antone's/Paul Mitchell/Lonnie Brooks interview, Lonnie w/Kelller bros. (Box 2, Item 18a)
  - Lonnie Brooks w/Keller brothers-wide shot at Antone's – mix of board and mic. (Box 2, Item 18b)
  - Carlos Barbosa interview ext. Guerro's, April 13, 2003 (Box 2, Item 19-1-a)
  - Carlos Barbosa interview ext. Guerro's – wide shot, April 13, 2003 (Box 2, Item 19-1-b)
  - Derek O'Brien interview at Antone's, April 17, 2003 (Box 2, Item 20a)
  - Derek interview at Antone's, April 17, 2003 (Box 2, Item 20b)
  - Little Daddy and Sugar Bear at the Shoe Shine Shop, April 17, 2003 (Box 2, Item 21a)
  - Little Daddy and Sugar Bear, April 17, 2003 (Box 2, Item 21b)
  - B-roll of Little Daddy, April 17, 2003 (Box 2, Item 21-1)
  - Lucky [Tomblin] with Clifford and alone, April 17, 2003 (Box 2, Item 22a)
  - Lucky [Tomblin] interview, April 17, 2003 (Box 2, Item 22b)
  - Blues Boy Hubbard concert, Major D's, April 19, 2003 (Box 2, Item 23a)
  - Blues Boy Hubbard concert, Major D's, April 19, 2003 (Box 2, Item 23b)
  - Doyle Bramhall Sr. gig at Continental Club, April 19, 2003 (Box 2, Item 24a)
  - Doyle Bramhall Sr. gig at Continental Club, April 19, 2003 (Box 2, Item 24b)
  - Keller Brothers interview at Threadgill's, April 20. 2003 (Box 2, Item 25-1a)
  - Keller Brothers interview at Threadgill's, April 20. 2003 (Box 2, Item 25-1b)
  - end of Keller Brothers interview/Jane Bond interview, April 20. 2003 (Box 2, Item 26-2a)
  - end of Keller Brothers interview/Jane Bond interview, April 20. 2003 (Box 2, Item 26-2b)
  - Toni Price interview Arlyn Studio, April 21, 2003 (Box 2, Item 27-3a)
  - Toni Price interview Arlyn Studio, April 21, 2003 (Box 2, Item 27-3b)
  - Lavelle White, April 21, 2003 (Box 2, Item 28-4a)
  - Lavelle White up til after Clifford, April 21, 2003 (Box 2, Item 28-4b)
  - Lavelle White end/ Derek O'Brien, April 21, 2003 (Box 2, Item 29-5a)
  - Lavelle White end, April 21, 2003 (Box 2, Item 29-5b)
  - Eve Monsees and Gary Clark, April 21, 2003 (Box 3, Item 30-6a)
  - Eve Monsees and Gary Clark, April 21, 2003 (Box 3, Item 30-6b)
  - Lewis Black interview, April 22, 2003 (Box 3, Item 31-7a)
  - Lewis Black interview, April 22, 2003 (Box 3, Item 31-7b)
  - Chris Layton interview at Antone's Records, April 22, 2003 (Box 3, Item 32-8a)
  - Chris Layton interview at Antone's Records, April 22, 2003 (Box 3, Item 32-8b)
  - Denny Freeman interview at Antone's Records, April 22, 2003 (Box 3, Item 33-9a)
  - Denny Freeman interview at Antone's Records, April 22, 2003 (Box 3, Item 33-9b)
  - Kim Wilson and Clifford at office, camera only, April 22, 2003 (Box 3, Item 34-10a)
  - Denny Freeman cont.'d, Antone's Tour, camera only, April 22, 2003 (Box 3, Item 34-10b)
  - Jake Andrews, April 22, 2003 (Box 3, Item 35-11a)
  - Jake Andrews at Antone's, April 22, 2003 (Box 3, Item 35-11b)
  - Jake Andrews continued, April 22, 2003 (Box 3, Item 36-12a)
  - Jake Andrews continued, April 22, 2003 (Box 3, Item 36-12b)
  - Paul Ray and The Cobras at Continental Club, April 22, 2003 (Box 3, Item 37-13a)
  - Paul Ray and The Cobras at Continental Club, April 22, 2003 (Box 3, Item 37-13b)
  - Joe Ely interview at Backyard, April 23, 2003 (Box 3, Item 38-14a)
  - Joe Ely interview at Backyard, April 23, 2003 (Box 3, Item 38-14b)
  - Joe Ely, April 23, 2003 (Box 3, Item 39-14:40a)
  - Joe Ely, April 23, 2003 (Box 3, Item 39-14:40b)
  - Marcia Ball interview, April 23, 2003 (Box 3, Item 40-15a)
  - Marcia Ball interview, April 23, 2003 (Box 3, Item 40-15b)
  - end of Marcia Ball/Paul Ray, April 23, 2003 (Box 3, Item 41-16a)
  - end of Marcia Ball/Paul Ray, April 23, 2003 (Box 3, Item 41-16b)
  - Paul Ray, April 23, 2003 (Box 3, Item 42a)
  - Paul Ray, April 23, 2003 (Box 3, Item 42b)
  - Ray Benson, April 23, 2003 (Box 3, Item 43a)
  - Ray Benson, April 23, 2003 (Box 3, Item 43b)
  - Ray Benson, April 23, 2003 (Box 3, Item 44a)
  - Ray Benson end, April 23, 2003 (Box 3, Item 44b)
  - Kim Wilson interview, April 23, 2003 (Box 3, Item 45-20a)
  - Kim Wilson interview, April 24, 2003 (Box 4, Item 45-20b)
  - Kim Wilson interview, April 24, 2003 (Box 4, Item 46-21a)
  - Kim Wilson interview, April 24, 2003 (Box 4, Item 46-21b)
  - Kim Wilson interview, April 24, 2003 (Box 4, Item 47-22a)
  - Kim Wilson interview, April 24, 2003 (Box 4, Item 47-22b)
  - Kim Wilson concert in Dallas, April 24, 2003 (Box 4, Item 48-23a)
  - Kim Wilson concert in Dallas, April 24, 2003 (Box 4, Item 48-23b)
  - Steve Berlin/David Hidalgo, April 25, 2003 (Box 4, Item 49-0a)
  - Steve Berlin/David Hidalgo, April 25, 2003 (Box 4, Item 49-0b)
  - Ian Moore, April 25, 2003 (Box 4, Item 50-1a)
  - Ian Moore, April 25, 2003 (Box 4, Item 50-1b)
  - Susan Tedeschi, April 25, 2003 (Box 4, Item 51-2a)
  - Susan Tedeschi, April 25, 2003 (Box 4, Item 51-2b)
  - Charles Attal and West Side Horns, April 25, 2003 (Box 4, Item 52-3a)
  - Charles Attal and West Side Horns, April 25, 2003 (Box 4, Item 52-3b)
  - Los Lobos, concert A cam, April 25, 2003 (Box 4, Item 53-4a)
  - Los Lobos, April 25, 2003 (Box 4, Item 53-4b)
  - Buddy Guy interview, May 10, 2003 (Box 4, Item 54-5a)
  - Buddy Guy interview, May 10, 2003 (Box 4, Item 54-5b)
  - Marcia Ball gig (Box 4, Item 55a)
  - Marcia Ball gig (Box 4, Item 55b)
  - Marcia Ball gig, Blue Monday (Box 4, Item 56b)
  - Clifford interview at his apartment, camera only, June 1, 2003 (Box 4, Item 58a)
  - Clifford interview sharing photos; Clifford in club for the first time in 3 years, June 1, 2003 (Box 4, Item 59-2a)
  - Clifford walking into club for the first time in 3 years, June 2, 2003 (Box 4, Item 60-3)
  - First time in club (wireless), June 2, 2003 (Box 4, Item 61a)
  - First time in club (with boom), June 2, 2003 (Box 4, Item 61b)
  - Antone's show, first day Clifford is back, June 2, 2003 (Box 4, Item 61c)
  - First time in club (wireless), June 2, 2003 (Box 4, Item 62a)
  - First time in club (with boom), June 2, 2003 (Box 4, Item 62b)
  - Antone's show (JIB) -First time Clifford back in 3 years, June 2, 2003 (Box 5, Item 62c)
  - First time in club (wireless) A-6 -Lee Ann Atherton – Try a Little Tenderness, Larry Fulcher - Malford Milligan- Blow Wind Blow, Sugar Bear, June 2, 2003 (Box 5, Item 63a)
  - First time in club boom B-3, June 2, 2003 (Box 5, Item 63b)
  - First time in club (JIB) C-3, June 2, 2003 (Box 5, Item 63c)
  - first time in club A-7, June 2, 2003 (Box 5, Item 64a)
  - first time in club (boom) B-4, June 2, 2003 (Box 5, Item 64b)
  - first time in club (JIB) C-4, June 2, 2003 (Box 5, Item 64c)
  - first time in club 8-A, June 2, 2003 (Box 5, Item 65a)
  - first time in club (JIB) C-5, June 2, 2003 (Box 5, Item 65c)
  - first time in club-end of night A-9, June 2, 2003 (Box 5, Item 66a)
  - first time in club (JIB) C-6, June 2, 2003 (Box 5, Item 66c)
  - West Side Horns interview (ends before B camera), June 3, 2003 (Box 5, Item 67a)
  - West Side Horns interview B-1 (continued after A camera), June 3, 2003 (Box 5, Item 67b)
  - End of West Side Horns interview/Beginning Eddie Wilson, June 3, 2003 (Box 5, Item 68a)
  - End of West Side Horns interview/Beginning Eddie Wilson, June 3, 2003 (Box 5, Item 68b)
  - end of Eddie Wilson with Clifford, June 3, 2003 (Box 5, Item 69a)
  - end of Eddie Wilson with Clifford, June 3, 2003 (Box 5, Item 69b)
  - Clifford in front of first location of Club (6th st) talking about the early days, June 4, 2003 (Box 5, Item 70)
  - Clifford at the second club location (Anderson Ln.), June 4, 2003 (Box 5, Item 71)
  - Clifford driving, third location (Guadalupe) (Box 5, Item 72)
  - Clifford in record store and clothing store part 1, A-camera only, June 5, 2003 (Box 5, Item 73)
  - Clifford in record store part 2, A-camera only, June 5, 2003 (Box 5, Item 74)
  - Billy Gibbons interview, June 13, 2003 (Box 5, Item 75a)
  - Billy Gibbons interview, June 13, 2003 (Box 5, Item 75b)
  - Pinetop Perkins #1 (arrival), June 17, 2003 (Box 5, Item 76)
  - Pinetop Perkins #2 (hotel), June 17, 2003 (Box 5, Item 77)
  - Gene Taylor interview, June 19, 2003 (Box 5, Item 78-1a)
  - Gene Taylor interview, June 19, 2003 (Box 5, Item 78-1b)
  - Gene Taylor interview, June 19, 2003 (Box 5, Item 79-2a)
  - Gene Taylor interview, June 19, 2003 (Box 5, Item 79-2b)
  - Sarah Brown interview, June 18, 2003 (Box 6, Item 80-1a)
  - Sarah Brown interview, June 18, 2003 (Box 6, Item 80-1b)
  - Sarah Brown interview, June 18, 2003 (Box 6, Item 81-2a)
  - Sarah Brown interview, June 18, 2003 (Box 6, Item 81-2b)
  - Pinetop Perkins interview, June 18, 2003 (Box 6, Item 82a)
  - Pinetop Perkins interview, June 18, 2003 (Box 6, Item 82b)
  - Pinetop Perkins interview part 2 (playing), June 18, 2003 (Box 6, Item 83a)
  - Pinetop Perkins interview part 2 (playing), June 18, 2003 (Box 6, Item 83b)
  - Pinetop Perkins & Gatemouth Brown sound check with Clifford, June 19, 2003 (Box 6, Item 84)
  - Gatemouth Brown interview, June 19, 2003 (Box 6, Item 85a)
  - Gatemouth Brown interview, June 19, 2003 (Box 6, Item 85b)
  - Pinetop Perkins set part 1, June 19, 2003 (Box 6, Item 86a)
  - Pinetop Perkins set part 1 stereo mix, June 19, 2003 (Box 6, Item 86b)
  - Pinetop Perkins set part 2, June 19, 2003 (Box 6, Item 87a)
  - Pinetop Perkins set part 2 stereo mix, June 19, 2003 (Box 6, Item 87b)
  - Gatemouth Brown concert, June 19, 2003 (Box 6, Item 88a)
  - Gatemouth Brown concert stereo mix, June 19, 2003 (Box 6, Item 88b)
  - Willie Nelson interview (Willie audio only), July 9, 2003 (Box 6, Item 89a)
  - Willie Nelson interview (Clifford audio only), July 9, 2003 (Box 6, Item 89b)
  - Ray Benson solo, July 10, 2003 (Box 6, Item 91a)
  - Ray Benson solo cam, July 10, 2003 (Box 6, Item 91b)
  - Ray Benson solo-board mix with live, July 10, 2003 (Box 6, Item 91c)
  - Billy Joe Shaver concert, July 10, 2003 (Box 6, Item 92a)
  - Billy Joe Shaver concert, July 10, 2003 (Box 6, Item 92b)
  - Billy Joe Shaver concert-board and live mix *production audio, July 10, 2003 (Box 6, Item 92c)
  - Billy Joe Shaver interview/Eve playing with Clifford (partial), July 10, 2003 (Box 6, Item 93a)
  - Clifford's All Stars/ Clifford on stage with Eve Monsees, July 10, 2003 (Box 6, Item 93b)
  - Clifford and Eve (board and live mix) *production audio, July 10, 2003 (Box 7, Item 93c)
  - Clifford at radio station with Jody part 1 (camera mic) A-cam only, July 11, 2003 (Box 7, Item 94)
  - Clifford at radio station with Jody part 2 (camera mic) A-cam only, July 11, 2003 (Box 7, Item 95)
  - 5 min Clifford at end of Doyle's show; Andy Langer interview, July 12-13, 2003 (Box 7, Item 96a)
  - Doyle Bramhall Sr. interview at Threadgill's part 1 of 2, July 13, 2003 (Box 7, Item 97a)
  - Doyle Bramhall Sr. interview part 1, July 13, 2003 (Box 7, Item 97b)
  - Doyle Bramhall Sr. interview part 2, July 13, 2003 (Box 7, Item 98a)
  - Doyle Bramhall Sr. interview part 2, July 13, 2003 (Box 7, Item 98b)
  - Eve Monsees concert, July 13, 2003 (Box 7, Item 98-1a)
  - Eve Monsees concert, July 13, 2003 (Box 7, Item 98-1b)
  - Los Lonely Boys concert, July 13, 2003 (Box 7, Item 98-2a)
  - Los Lonely Boys concert and interview, July 13, 2003 (Box 7, Item 98-2b)
  - Los Lonely Boys part 2, July 13, 2003 (Box 7, Item 98-3a)
  - Los Lonely Boys part 2, July 13, 2003 (Box 7, Item 98-3b)
  - Los Lonely Boys interview/ Little Rod interview, July 13, 2003 (Box 7, Item 98-4a)
  - Sue Foley interview, July 14, 2003 (Box 7, Item 99a)
  - Sue Foley interview, July 14, 2003 (Box 7, Item 99b)
  - Doyle Bramhall II interview, July 14, 2003 (Box 7, Item 100a)
  - Doyle Bramhall II interview, July 14, 2003 (Box 7, Item 100b)
  - Sue Foley concert, July 14, 2003 (Box 7, Item 101a)
  - Sue Foley concert, July 14, 2003 (Box 7, Item 101b)
  - Sue Foley concert *production audio –board & live mix, July 14, 2003 (Box 6, Item 101c)
  - Sue Foley concert, July 14, 2003 (Box 6, Item 102-2a)
  - Sue Foley concert, July 14, 2003 (Box 7, Item 102-2b)
  - Sue Foley concert, July 14, 2003 (Box 7, Item 102-2c)
  - Blue Monday set, July 14, 2003 (Box 7, Item 103a)
  - Blue Monday set – jam session, July 14, 2003 (Box 7, Item 103b)
  - Blue Monday, July 14, 2003 (Box 7, Item 103c)
  - Angela Strehli interview part 1 of 2, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 104a)
  - Angela Strehli interview, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 104b)
  - Angela Strehli interview part 2 of 2, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 105a)
  - Angela Strehli interview part 2 of 2, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 105b)
  - Jimmie Vaughan and Lou Ann Barton interview, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 106a)
  - Jimmie and Lou Ann interview, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 106b)
  - Jimmie and Lou Ann interview, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 106c)
  - A-camera only-Hubert Sumlin, Calvin Jones, Willie Smith with Clifford at hotel- part 1, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 107)
  - A-camera only-Hubert Sumlin, Willie Smith, Calvin Jones, w/Clifford part 2 -David Adelson interview, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 108)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 109a)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 109b)
  - Antone's Show 1 of 5, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 109c)
  - Antone's Show 1 of 5, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 109d)
  - Antone's Show *production audio, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 109e)
  - Antone's Show 2 of 5, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 110a)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 110b)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 6, Item 110c)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 6, Item 110d)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 110e)
  - Antone's Show 3 of 5, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 111a)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 111b)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 111c)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 6, Item 111d)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 6, Item 111e)
  - Antone's Show 4 of 5, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 112a)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 112b)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 112c)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 112d)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 112e)
  - Antone's Show 5 of 5, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 113a)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 8, Item 113b)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 9, Item 113c)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 9, Item 113d)
  - Antone's Show, July 15, 2003 (Box 9, Item 113e)
  - Calvin Jones and Willie Smith interview at club, July 16, 2003 (Box 9, Item 114a)
  - Calvin Jones and Willie Smith interview at club, July 16, 2003 (Box 9, Item 114b)
  - Ruby's – Clifford/Kim Wilson/Angela Strehli/Derek O'Brien/ Willie Smith/Calvin Jones, July 16, 2003 (Box 9, Item 115-1a)
  - Ruby's – main audio for both with " ", July 16, 2003 (Box 9, Item 115-1b)
  - Ruby's – part 2 of 3, July 16, 2003 (Box 9, Item 116-2a)
  - Ruby's – main audio, party, July 16, 2003 (Box 9, Item 116-2b)
  - Ruby's – main audio part 3 of 3, July 16, 2003 (Box 9, Item 117-3a)
  - Ruby's main audio, July 16, 2003 (Box 9, Item 117-3b)
  - A camera only – Southern Feeling 1 of 2, July 16, 2003 (Box 9, Item 118)
  - A camera only – Southern Feeling and Clifford playing part 2 of 2, July 16, 2003 (Box 9, Item 119)
  - Kaz interview, July 17, 2003 (Box 9, Item 120a)
  - Kaz interview, July 17, 2003 (Box 9, Item 120b)
  - Jay Moeller interview, July 17, 2003 (Box 9, Item 121a)
  - Jay Moeller interview, July 17, 2003 (Box 9, Item 121b)
  - Toni Price concert 1 of 2, July 17, 2003 (Box 9, Item 122a)
  - Toni Price concert 1 tape only audio from board, July 17, 2003 (Box 9, Item 122b)
  - Toni Price concert-end of night – B cam only / 2 of 2, July 17, 2003 (Box 9, Item 123)
  - Vallejo interview and sound check, July 18, 2003 (Box 9, Item 124a)
  - Vallejo interview and sound check, B cam, July 18, 2003 (Box 9, Item 124b)
  - A camera only – Vallejo concert 5 – 6 min, July 18, 2003 (Box 9, Item 125)
  - Bill Bentley interview – A cam, July 19, 2003 (Box 9, Item 126a)
  - Bill Bentley interview – Boom only, July 19, 2003 (Box 9, Item 126b)
  - Barbara Lynn interview (boom only), July 19, 2003 (Box 9, Item 127a)
  - Barbara Lynn interview, July 19, 2003 (Box 9, Item 127b)
  - Barbara Lynn concert/ backstage with Barb and Cliff – 1 of 2, July 19, 2003 (Box 9, Item 128a)
  - Barbara Lynn concert 1 of 2, July 19, 2003 (Box 9, Item 128b)
  - Barbara Lynn concert* production audio, July 19, 2003 (Box 10, Item 128c)
  - Barbara Lynn concert 2 of 2 - shots of Clifford listening, backstage with Barbara Lynn/Hubert Sumlin & Bill Bentley, July 19, 2003 (Box 10, Item 129a)
  - Barbara Lynn concert 2 of 2, July 19, 2003 (Box 10, Item 129b)
  - Barbara Lynn concert * production audio, July 19, 2003 (Box 10, Item 129c)
  - A camera only – Clifford listening to music a little backstage - Clifford w/ Hubert Sumlin 7-20-03, July 19, 2003 (Box 10, Item 130)
  - Hubert Sumlin interview, July 17, 2003 (Box 10, Item 131a)
  - Hubert Sumlin interview, July 17, 2003 (Box 10, Item 131b)
  - A camera only – John Paul Mitchell interview; split tracks (Box 10, Item 132)
  - Robert Rodriguez interview from beta (Box 10, Item 133)
  - A camera only club shots, July 18, 2003 (Box 10, Item 134)
  - Antone's Record store cutaways, April 21, 2003 (Box 10, Item 135)
  - Ironworks, B-roll (Box 10, Item 136)
  - Antone's posters, July 17, 2003 (Box 10, Item 139)
  - Antone's Home movies (Box 10, Item 140)
  - Doyle II part 1, July 14, 2003 (Box 10, Item 141a)
  - Doyle II performance, July 14, 2003 (Box 10, Item 141b)
  - Doyle II concert part 1 *production audio, July 14, 2003 (Box 10, Item 141c)
  - Doyle II concert, July 14, 2003 (Box 10, Item 142-2a)
  - Doyle II concert, July 14, 2003 (Box 10, Item 142-2b)
  - Doyle II concert, July 14, 2003 (Box 10, Item 142-2c)
  - Bobbie Nelson/ A – cam, tape 1 (Box 10, Item 143a)
  - Bobbie Nelson/ B-cam, tape 1 (Box 10, Item 143b)
  - Road trip to Vinton LA and Port Arthur TX, B& B, Lou Ann's, Big Oaks, March 17-18, 2004 (Box 10, Item 144)
  - Road trip- last part of Lou Ann's, Big Oaks, drive to Port Arthur – part 2, August 18, 2003 (Box 10, Item 145)
  - Road trip-drive around Port Arthur bridge/ signs/ family house / school/ liquor store – part 3, August 19, 2003 (Box 10, Item 146)